Hello, welcome to the SDM 32, Cuba makes five on cube I.D. Eco's.
I'm glad you've made a decision to join thousands of other student who have enjoyed millions of quality
training minutes on this channel.
This course teaches you how to build embedded systems, firmware unpaired for drivers using the SDM
data, Cuban Mics five framework and the SDM 32 Kupe IDP development environment.
This course has many sections, but primarily the cause can be divided into three parts.
The first parts, those with perforin driver development.
In this part, we master how to use the SDM headed to Cuba, mix framework to set up clocks and Reges
the parameters of our peripheral drivers and then go on to the cube.
IDG Development Environment.
To complete the development and testing of the peripheral drivers, we show master different setup configurations
of our peripheral drivers.
In this part, the inspired Froese include the the USP, the P.W. and the S.P.I, the ADC, a U.
OT, the DME, etc..
The second part of this must of course, deals with developing embedded firmware applications using
some of the middleware provided by the SDM 32 queue remix framework, one of psychomotor where we sure
must not use the free Arktos real time canno.
We shall see how to use SDM headed to Cuba mix to create tasks, semaphores and other cannel components
for real time firmware development.
We should also see how to develop these canno components from scratch using only the cube IP development
environment.
Finally, the third part of the course deals with working with the Cube.
IDG as a standalone development environment over here, we shall see how to develop a metal embedded
C firmware and drivers without using any libraries.
We shall literally download the microcontrollers data sheet and develop our firmware and drive us using
information from the data sheets only.
We should then go on to use this same data sheet information to develop firmware and perfect drivers
using arm assembly language.
By the end of this course, you'd learn how to develop USP drivers and firmware and some of the practical
examples we showed.
Take a look at is building a USP, HD Mauer's device and a keyboard USP device, as well as configuring
your USP for virtual import.
Also, you would master the ADC driver and firmware development.
And we're going to take a look at different configurations of the ATC.
We're going to see how to convert, use and interrupt using the DMA and how to use multiple channels
of the ADC.
Further, you would also mosta time driver development and over here as well, which shall see different
configurations of the time timer configurations such as input, capture, interrupt mode and using the
time to count event.
Also, you'll be able to develop drivers for the S.P.I peripheral and just like the other peripherals,
we shall see different modes of configuration.
We shall see how to transfer, use and interrupt using the DMA and use in pooling.
Furthermore, you would be able to build bare metal embedded C firmware and drivers without using any
libraries using the Kubi D E only.
Also, you'll be able to create embedded drivers using arm assembly language from scratch without using
any libraries.
You will also be able to build Real-Time Firmware using the free Archos.
You'd be able to create your own tasks.
You'll be able to synchronize tasks.
You'll be able to use semaphores Mbewe takes and in fact, you'll be able to send notification between
tasks.
And then lastly, you'll be able to beaute other drivers, such as the you auto driver, and you'll
be able to configure it to work in different configuration modes such as DMA, poulain, interrupt,
etc..
Please take a look at the full course curriculum.
I have no doubt you would love this course.
Also, it comes with a full money back guarantee for 30 days.
So you've got nothing to lose.